(Sheldon:)And that made you feel sad?
(Leonard:)- Yes.
- I knew it.
(Sheldon:)Just keep going.
I guess I'm good at this.
(Amy:)It's just, I thought they liked
hanging out with me...
...but I guess I was fooling myseIf.
(Sheldon:)When they were over here...
(Sheldon:)...did you fail to offer them
a beverage?
Because I can see how that could stick
in someone's craw.
Sheldon, I'm gonna ask you something,
and I'd like you to keep an open mind.
AIways.
(Amy:)At this moment,
I find myseIf craving human intimacy...
(Amy:)...and physical contact.
(Sheldon:)Oh, boy.
(Sheldon:)You know ours is a relationship
of the mind.
Proposal:
One wild night of torrid lovemaking...
(Amy:)...that soothes my soul
and inflames my loins.